Welcome to Psyche Awakens, a show in the panel verse where tarot, truth and raw conversation meet.
We explore boldly, we disagree intelligently and we protect the circle.
Here's how we roll.
House rules.
Debate ideas, not people.
No doxing, slander, hate or threats, ever.
Bring receipts, claims need sources or timestamps, no rumour relays, signal discipline, mix muted
and less called, no spam, no derail, the mods are the guardians, warning, time out, ban,
no negotiations, mid-show.
This is Psyche's channel, Psyche's Rules.
He keeps it safe, sharp and on topic.
Use common sense and be respectful to everyone and you will be fine.
Contribute or be entertained welcome if you're here to sow chaos hang out. There's a place for you here, too
Now welcome your host psyche. See ya storyteller and your host eat truth first shadow second
Let's get into it
bathed in waters naked wise lightning cracks across the skies the
thunderstorm is me
Flesh and sky the vision now is read
Yeah
Hello, hold on
Everyone's quiet so far let me see. Oh, I do have this
Many until 20 people get in here, then I have a premiere. Hey, what's up?
awful channel. Oh my gosh, well, you're an awful person and
awful people aren't allowed here only really cool people are here and so
You're gonna be kicked out. Is it a funny though? The people that are here first are like the haters. Isn't that funny?
They're just like ready to go, right?
Haters had their coffee this morning, right?
Yeah, then don't bother coming back swagura. You're gonna be a
Sacrifice to the cult. Okay?
Hey guys, good morning. It's not a bad day. You know, I did have like three people so far this morning come look for scrap metal. So
Kind of
Even with the average scrap metal looking people. Oh my gosh, you know
You're wasting these people's time and plus, you know, this guy has his granddaughter with him
He couldn't be taking her to the park and stuff and
You know spending time with his granddaughter
But he's ends up having to just bang on a door and
You know, she's like what? It's like really sad
It's really sad, and then there's no scrap metal here.
So grandpa, grandpa didn't walk away with anything.
But anyway, so, oh look, and yeah,
oh they are, yeah, and the haters start to leave too.
There we go.
Hi, wow, my channel sucks,
and we're sending more people over.
Okay, good, no good, that's why I have moderators.
That's why I have moderators.
Yeah, Jared Loser.
Absolute loser absolute loser. I've got more good people than bad people. The good people are just getting their coffee though
They'll be in soon shortly. But yeah, the haters had their coffee, too
Jared what a loser a little absolute loser
Can you imagine guys just sitting around waiting for someone to come on and to say something stupid and then you know
Okay, it's okay. I have my avocado toast this morning
Let's have a look at this. It's like a
This is better to me than like a no engagement ring
Oh gosh, this looks good. It looks good, huh?
Yeah, if I could have somebody that's a friend of mine actually like say something
Say hello to me or something or is it all haters right now? Maybe all haters. They're saying there's any people over
Wow, it absolute losers or more people are being sent over. So it's that's the AMC of course
He's like, oh, I'm just happy. He thinks everybody's me and everybody is him
Nobody hardly anybody else is such a loser
They have time to sit around wait for somebody to show that they don't like to come on so they can say something stupid in the room
But I do have a new song premiering right now. I think you guys will enjoy it. It's a
I can't even tell you you'll hear what it is. You'll hear what it is. It's gonna be it's based on last night's show
We had some great shows last night by the way. We had a flirty diamond in auto
Me little hints about what the song is about. It's a love story for the ages wait till 20 people get in here
Hello, Maddie aka the Joker. How are you?
Maddie ice are you a nice person or I've never seen you before but welcome to the show. Okay?
Um, everything's working out for me. Everything's working out. You know, I was kind of worried about some things and then, you know, some things work themselves out
um, I
Want to thank the people that helped make that happen
So I can have a breakfast today and things like that. And so I appreciate everybody
Thank you Barry the turtle for
buying the reading yesterday for that
You know the reading was unfortunately for some hag
some evil hag, I don't even want to get into it, but okay.
Enjoy the people at your door, okay.
Well, we can see, okay, so 21 people in here.
Hello, hello, hello, okay.
Let's see, I can play it now.
Enjoy this song.
In the glow of neon, she's cutting the knife
A blade in her hand, a fire in her eyes so bright
He shows up in red, with a hose and a grin
But he's in
Flirty diamond, all those flames
He called her dirty, but he'll learn her name
He was straight till she spun him around
Now he's burning in love
Where the fire is shone
laughs like a secret, sharp as a knife, but maybe she's tired of the dangerous life.
He drops his shirt with a volunteer's pride, she smiles.
very romantic I did electronic mariachi and salsa style so hope you like that
I'll play it later hmm how are we doing guys hey what's up J-dog happy Monday
everyone it is a nice Monday I slept to some like really good Indian like Hindu
J-Dog is a good dude and the more people try to convince me that he's not the more I like him so
Keep a keep dogging on my my dog. Hey mason's here
Let me see let me see he's gonna come up in a second. Here we go. I love mason's
Uh-oh, oh there he is hello
Thank you Mason. What's up?
Hey, thank you. Yeah, do you hear the song?
So I keep so I hear
What I can't hear you say it again, so I keep what's talking about I just play it. So you're just playing yeah, it was flirty diamond and auto song
Hmm so I get that I heard a song go actually playing this little wallet girl. It was it was I was just playing it
It was a flirty diamond auto song.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, shoot, it's a little bit warm.
Yeah, everything's working out though.
I was kind of, you know, I was kind of worried yesterday.
I was like, but everything's working out.
Everything's working out.
So how was your night, Mason?
It's okay, but I was wondering what happened to Otto.
What happened with Otto?
What happened to the other person?
I think it was like...
Flirty?
Well flirty and auto. I mean I have another version of the song. I'll have a shorter version. I'll play it here. I
This might be like a little bit faster because it's a shorter song. So
Let me put it on
Yeah, flirty diamond in auto. It's a love story for the ages. Did you see what do you see them last night? They were you know
It's true love. I think
Let's see
Here we go. Yeah
Almost there. Oh
He lost Mason. Okay. Well, hopefully he enjoys this song. This is the
world premiere of the second version of Otto and flirty
In the glow of knee
She's caught in the night, a blade in her hand, a fire in her eyes so bright, he shows up in red, with a hose and a...
like a secret sharp as a knife but maybe she's tired of the dangers life he
drops his shirt with a volunteer's pride she smirks
She's a wild card queen, he's a rescue man
To misfits dance and wear the store
Thank you!
How'd you like that?
Yeah, those are good songs, man.
I liked that first one and that second one.
They're hella good, man.
Yeah, they have a new engine.
Like they let me use, I was like using four,
but I wasn't allowed to use five,
but they let me use six today.
So yeah, I, I believe it was a better quality.
The song is pretty catchy.
Yeah, it is.
I thought so.
Hey, what's up, Amber?
How are you?
Oh
Dude that was that was a really good last night. I don't flirty diamond, bro
Do my my I was on there and my thing dropped and I was like, oh damn
I had to go recharge my shit and then you know, I was just watching the content too, bro
That was some good content last night. It was yeah, that was pretty crazy. I mean
Yeah, that's good love story, man
Wow
I was pretty shocked, you know, he's I think she turned him
Well, I don't know what she turned him. Good to see everybody. Thank you for coming
Yeah, I did have the scrap metal people here this morning
Well, there's one guy with his granddaughter, you know, and he's like, oh, we're gonna go to the park in a few minutes
We were just gonna get some scrap metal from this guy and it's like what you're wasting like this grandfather granddaughter's time
you know the quality time sending him on a wild goose chase to
to like pick up the metal from my house and you know
So yeah, you're working last night. I mean it was crazy. It was just crazy, but uh
I mean shit
Yeah, they had that happen to me too, bro
They sent scrap metals to fucking my old address too when I was living at the other spot. They fucking
Called scrap metal. They had people try to pick up my ice cream trucks. They had people try to fucking
All kinds of bullshit, bro. All kinds of stupid shit. I mean, it's like, okay
I mean, it's like I should just put a sign out. I think I will put a sign out there that says, you know
yeah no free stuff yeah I'll put up I'll tell the story like what happened on
the sign and I'll say hey I have this like there's this like incel loser that
has nothing better to do but you know harass me
Do you believe he was a mailman?
Yeah, Tony the conductor that was one of that was his job, I don't know if he's still that right now to this day
I don't think so because he seems unemployed right now. You know, he's on here harassing people all the time now
Tony the conductor is more than just me. Oh
Dude, he's just he goes in everybody's chat leg
Everybody's under all that my call alt. What's that other one? Oh, yeah
Yeah, he'll he'll do all kinds of all can just be talking shit all day 24 seven like don't matter what time of day it is
Oh, no, no, he no he is obsessed with you. Yeah, you're like the main one like he's like
He does have a whole channel just dedicated to me. It's kind of flattering though
And it's like, you know, it's like it is my clips and so it's like it's not like
I mean, are they bad clips or are they just kind of like like well
It's like anything that I put on my show
I mean I put I showed the good the bad the ugly about myself and so you know
Maybe you can like you know just take out the ugly parts or you know
Put them put them on a channel and it's like whatever but it's like you know
Everyone when you're on for like I was on for 12 hours a day at one point, right? So you're gonna find you're gonna find
You know things that don't
I don't know. I don't think they're that bad. He does he does have my front door on one of the channels
And so that's kind of like, you know, I would say that's disturbing. Yeah
Yeah, and then he was in here like he's the first person in the chat and stuff like that. I think he's pretty obsessed
Dude, I think he's in love with you, bro
Yeah, I think he's in love with you and he's upset because he can't have you be that obsessed with somebody like unless you like there's some kind of like
You know true emotion down there. I mean he must be using lust maybe but I turned him down
Yeah, I think that's what hurts him right now
Like the way groovy Jimmy because RG black RG is a homosexual closet homosexual groovy Jimmy
He tried to go after groovy Jimmy groovy Jimmy says he don't get down that way
Same thing and now he's obsessed with them same thing with
This guy, the way he is with you. Same exact shit.
That's what happens, these closets, the homeless, well Tony's not a closet, he's out of it now, but
these guys, they get obsessed with people online and then they stalk them and harass them and, you know, it becomes an obsession.
It's crazy, man.
Hold on, I'm gonna just delete the comment.
This is not appropriate. Oh, I know you I need to show actually. Yeah, some of the bad comments
I don't even see I need to put it on at all. Okay, there we go. I can I can hide the person
Okay, just delete that
comment
There we go
Yeah, cuz I do like to protect people, you know in the chat
And so I'm sorry if I haven't done a great job of it before I'll try to keep a better job
No slandering anybody like my my chef. Yeah, so how are you doing? Oh, it's another day, man
Just been busy with this holiday season
What do you what are you right now second? Oh avocado bagel looks good
Hell yeah, psyche
Bro have you noticed that everybody you know like have you noticed like the evolution of psyche like have you ever thought about going like a
Maybe like a little short clip or like a little video of you like from when you first started
Podcasting when you first were on the air to the way you are now like everything about you has changed as far as like from
The way you talk to the way you dress the way you carry yourself to just everything and now you're just more like you're cutting eggs
you're you're you're
You're very different now. You're very stern now like a more stern like I'll just say it like that
More like Jerry Springer Howard Stern more
And it's a yeah, it's a good thing and it's really really good some people don't like it
But I enjoy the fuck out of it, bro. Yeah, I think it's a change for the good and I think like, you know
I was more like, you know, had a awareness
that I was on camera at the beginning
and I was not really used to being on camera.
I used to be really shy.
I used to like not, or I used to not be able
to like watch myself back and stuff like that.
Now I,
No, I can't and I
Well, nobody should be embarrassed to be on camera because we look in the mirror every day
We get up we brush our kids we take a shower
You know we shave we do whatever we got to do in the morning. We see ourselves in the mirror every day
So why are we so embarrassed to show ourselves on camera? Like why would anybody be embarrassed like like?
If you're that embarrassed to go don't don't be on here like if you're gonna be on here to do some bad stuff
And you don't want to be a genuine person
Then they don't need to be on here
Yeah
And it's like you know, they do have like I'm getting a lot more attention right now sometimes the negative
But you know the people that love me like
like so many people in this chat it's like I've had really great chats lately
there's a lot less of the trolling because it's basically just one one person doing it right
yeah he's a sock fuck that one man it takes fucking Tony the conductor
and that's a chapter in my whole in my uh in my book um
Trollopedia there's a whole chapter on the sock puppet troll
That's a great example of what he is basically the sock puppet is someone with a bunch of alternative accounts
And they'll go do like kind of like a echo chamber of the comment like oh, yeah, he's right
He's right or look let's come to you to say the same things
Once I block them, but eventually he'll run out of accounts. I think like I think it's getting less and less
So, you know, he basically should get a life and stop, like, you know, something that doesn't
mind.
Hi, Sponky.
Hi, Natalie.
And he's definitely...
Call me the cat or salute the call me.
I mean, it's like...
and sending pizza, unpaid pizzas, but paid for fertilizer.
But the good thing is that somebody
that was looking for the scrap metal
took all the fertilizer, so the fertilizer's gone, you know?
They took it without your permission,
or you can't make it take it?
It was next to the dumpster, so.
Oh, okay, so they took it.
Oh, okay.
So, yeah, eventually it just disappeared,
but yeah, I could have just used that for a...
For my garden, I do have a garden in the backyard. I have a nice backyard and stuff like that
So I'm a very fortunate person no matter what and you know, I count my blessings more than I count my
curses whatever but
Here's Rudy look at Rudy here
Yesterday I had went to an Indian Reservation and I got the Indian weed. I'll show you this Indian
They're good
Dude, it's like really it's different than the weed that I get the dispensaries like it's really really weird
Oh, let me grab it. Cool
And there was like no labels on it or nothing like that. So I can't really tell like
Scream but and you can tell me the TXC. So I was kind of like weary side, you know, I bought half a gram
Try it. Oh, and it's pretty good
Yeah, if it works it works, right? Yeah, I had like the worst weed I ever had was like in Mexico. I was in Puerto Vallarta, and I
Was like really having withdrawals from like not having weed and so I couldn't go bungee jumping because I was not feeling well
Oh, my brothers and sisters found a guy in the beach. Oh, look at nice. It's a vape
It's pretty good. I like it
Yeah, kind of weird
Brought me some weed. It was like brown and then it's like I got a headache from smoking it, but oh shit
it was the
But yeah, I'm spoiled because I got we had the best weed in California. You know, it's just like six
Oh hell yeah, bro. The best weed is in Cali, bro. Like hell. Yeah
Yeah, I'm kind of spoiled with it
But it's almost like heroin. It's so strong. You know, it's like what I heard is that
This is what I heard, I don't know if it's true, so we'll take it with a grain of salt,
that the cartels spray fentanyl on the weed when it's like dried or there's cultivating
whatever it's doing, and then that's why it's so addicting, because when they sell it to
the dispensaries, it gets the people coming back, you know, like the crack, the cocaine
epidemic in the 80s, how it gets people coming back, I think that's kind of what they're
That's what I heard. I don't know if it's true. I don't think it's true, but I don't know. I'm pretty hooked on a very strong
Yeah
Oh, yeah, spunky like I've had people last week
Coming looking for scrap metal at my house because this guy's published an ad or something like that with like free scrap metal
They go to they go on Craigslist Marketplace they'll go on offer up and they'll make random ads
They'll put pictures of your house and then they'll put like random pictures of just random crap
And then they'll say this is right here. Just come pick it up. Don't even have to knock or whatever
Yeah, just well he was already today saying oh you're gonna get more people more people
It was at least three people today, but it's like, you know, they're usually there's very nice people. They there does
They're not to blame for it. I know that's why I'm not like calling the cops on them, right?
Oh, no, they didn't know they didn't know don't don't pull a beta beta went after the guy ran out there barefoot
She did that
She gave him a tip she was like i'm gonna give you a tip and stuff like that. She gave him like a 30 tip
So yeah, that's why the guy came back and he's had he bought weed and he wanted to smoke some weed with beta
but then beta shot him down and went chasing him and took a picture of his license plate and
Ran out best with it like a crazy person
Oh my god, that was funny. That was like a trip kick where it's like they did the scream
Yeah
Lady that was funny
I don't know like yesterday. I was at beat. I don't know if you knew I was at beat is yesterday. Um, what happened there?
Um, the same thing that happens every time like, you know, she's like bronze bird up talk over me and I had to you know
Eventually to say I can't speak and so I'm just gonna go
Why does he do that he comes on there and he tries to pull like you stupid motherfucker
You don't talk like China. He's trying to put on a front especially in front of the ladies. I can tell like
We both been the gel psyche. So you know, we can tell the difference between
the fake tough guys and the real tough guys.
The fake ones is what Bronzebird is.
Bronzebird is a folk front,
and he's trying to just put on a front in front of the ladies,
and it's really, really annoying.
It's like, okay, dude, you're going a little too far now.
You're trying too hard to just.
Guess let's psyche talk like why you why you trying to why are you trying to well the whole chat was like the whole chat
Was like let him speak like let it like like just do a one-on-one with the psyche and beta and then like yeah
The way it should be just you and her one-on-one to solve it. Yeah
Yeah, and then Christine was there say hey
Well, let's just do one at a time talk and if they don't want to kick him off the panel
But then he started talking over me
and then I was like okay well he's talking over me he's like I'm going to talk over you motherfucker
and I and it's like so I just left um but you know Haka Bita she but Bita should have
let them keep ranking and this and that like you're there to have a civil conversation trying to solve
things trying to get things figured out and sorted out and shit and i can't calm i came calm and if
you you know i don't know if it's going to be clipped or anything you can listen to that probably on
rumble you go i could probably look at at the rumble yeah it's on the rumble um you know i'm
They have like a bunch of people like, you know, I think probably Q and blogger and they got good times
The vegan paper
Right and I'm I'm honored that I'm part. Hello. Who is it?
Hi, I don't have any scrap metal. It was a it was a prank. I'm sorry
No, no, it's not here
Lo siento
Yeah, I mean that's how I have to do and it's like I mean that's basically
And then and then here's the crazy thing they think that that's funny like what is AMC going ha ha ha what you just told them
Sorry, they're not here
Yeah, it's a waste of time. It's like, you know how they can be spending time quality time together and send their chasing around scrap metal
Yeah, I get oh it's happened this is the fourth time today
It's okay. What if that guy was counting on that scrap metal money?
What if he was like, okay, daughter, like we're gonna go eat today
And then we're gonna go collect the scrap metal and go recycle it and hopefully we'll get some money
And that guy would came over there thinking he's gonna score and you know get some money
It's breaking them. It's like yeah, me really. It's like, yeah, it's hurting them. It's not hurting you
Yeah, it's like it's just hurting the people. Yeah, you're not wasting your gas
They're wasting their gas and time coming over there. Yeah
Yeah.
It's sad.
And then the lady, well, I hope that pizza people get the get the pizza.
I hope they get to keep the pizza at least, you know, because I'm, you know, from what
I heard, here's what I heard about when it when it goes to the Gordashes.
I've never worked for any of those services.
I don't know.
But when I heard friends work for them, they said that once the food leaves the building,
To serve to somebody else they're gonna throw it away. Yeah, they'll just sort of away. Yeah, I hope they hopefully the people
Yeah, they don't have to drive back to the restaurant and then they give it and they just throwing the trash and stuff
Hopefully, yeah, everything but um, yeah
Yeah, it's ridiculous. It's ridiculous, but
You know, what can I do?
I'm gonna probably put a note on the door sooner or later that says hey with an explanation, but it's just
Yeah, I hope I yeah, well, it's like I hope that they
They can pursue prosecute. What's his name? You know now
You know, and I never dox him and I'll put also he's putting privacy complaints on like every video
So I just delete videos and stuff like that. I mean, they're just false, you know
It's like but what is he putting like he owns the video like if he's the owner
There's some kind of like privacy complaint about it like but it's like whenever they do that they
They just like warned me first like I think it's like a two days
I have to like address it or something like that so I could just edit it out of the video or just delete the video
Yeah, don't even bother whether just delete it and take it down. That's all I that's what I would do. Yeah
Prosecuted well RG RG. It is some let me see the California laws for stalking or doxing and harassment
Let me see California's law about it. I mean, it's maybe it's a different
Probably a Massachusetts, I think but let me see California
Doxing law
Let me see, it says, in California, doxing is addressed under criminal harassment laws,
okay, recent civil bill allows victims to sue for damages up to $30,000 plus legal cost.
Doxing is a misdemeanor crime when it-
uses electronic communication to cause reasonable fear for safety with potential penalties of
jail time and fines. The new bill expands on this providing a civil path for victims to recover
damages for emotional distress, physical harm, and other losses caused by the exposure of their
private information.
Okay, what is it intentionally using electronic communication to place someone in reasonable fear for their safety or the safety of their family?
And so penalties, you know, up to year in county jail, you know, that's just, you know, of course, a pipe dream that that would ever happen.
But there are laws enforcing laws that's different.
But if I really was to pursue it, I do know some people, he's not California and yet, but there's laws in other states too.
And, uh, and there's crossing lines, you know, at least like I can like, uh, take steps towards, uh, take steps towards that.
And so I will be doing that. I do have his full information because he did a striking before.
So I have all his information and I am not afraid to use it.
He's not California. Yeah, that's what I'm hoping for a federal federal law soon. There probably will be a federal law soon
I think so. I think yeah, Trump just signed something that very similar to that, you know
So, um, yeah, we'll see we'll see we'll see
But it's super annoying. Let's see. So
What else? Hey, let's see. Have you sexually have you not sexually harassed on cam with what can be received as special needs?
I don't think so like what are you talking about you're talking about you're talking about mason
I'm so sick of people saying mason. It's that special needs obviously. He's super intelligent almost genius level
Dude Mason is not he's
He's what he's leading on more than he knows so I don't feel bad for that guy one bit
So everybody trying to say like oh poor him poor him. He's not Miguel
He's you know him and Miguel are two different ones Miguel. I feel bad for Mason. Yeah, he's cool
But I don't feel sympathy for him because I feel he's a lot smarter than he's letting on
Well, yeah, I mean, but I think that uh, let's see. What do you think that needs changing the uh police?
Please use force in uh in England
I know well they have because they have only clubs in England, huh?
They have like the Bobby the Bobby's have the those clubs. Oh, yeah, they have the bottom clubs
They beat the shit out of people with them clip. Well, because they don't have guns over there, huh?
They I don't believe they have guns over there. They don't believe in like the weapons in the european states
Yeah
So, and yeah, I worked out some of the stuff from last night that I was worried about.
So thankfully, hopefully, I can get her, I got charged $155 for some, something I could
sign up for a trial for, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know Mason is autistic, and that does not mean stupid, and Queen Natalie is autistic.
And that does.
She says as as burgers and you know, it's not it's like nothing to do with intelligence
It's like it's like a different way of processing information and things like that and usually a lot of times
It's just a learning curve. That's all it is. They don't mean nothing like they're dumb or not
It's just like a way of learning
But I'm very sick of like people saying the R word and stuff like that
It's like people that are like trying to help they say they're trying to help it's just like during PT Barnum, you know
where he'd have these shows,
but it's like these people were ostracized from the society.
And then he gave them like a avenue to make money,
to become kind of famous and almost admire stuff like that.
Yeah, he gave him a life. He gave him. He gave him hope something to look forward to something to be
Yeah, that's not nothing bad
Howard Stern with like, you know how his whack pack or whatever like they
Yeah, we're able to book thousands of dollar books gigs every weekend and look at Beetlejuice
Look what happened with Beetlejuice. Look at all these people. Yeah
And so, you know, I think that I'm into treating people like everybody else.
I'm not into, because some people say, oh, we'll just ostracize him from the community
or like, you know, and I don't believe in that.
I don't, I think that.
That's mean.
Yeah.
That was.
Yeah
Here's what he is right and I accept him for who he is and I I will protect them as much as I can
you know, but it is a it can be a cruel world and
You know, I'm gonna try to make it
Little bit easier and nicer of a world, you know, you know, I don't have a full bone in my body
I'm not I don't want to hurt anybody and if I feel like I was doing more harm than good
I would I would reconsider that but I feel like
Just treating people like everybody else so
Yeah, so what's the plan for today? It's like you just gonna chill out and hang out. Yeah
I mean, I woke up got my got my food and gonna have my avocado toast and I thought I'd just stream a little bit earlier today and
Catch up. Yeah. Yeah. So how about you? What's what you up to you?
You're gonna get ready to head out to work get ready to get with these ice cream and
I'll hit you later psyche. All right. Thank you. You have a great day J dog. You too man. I hit you later man. Have a good one
Yeah
So how's everyone else doing?
They're doing an outdoor screening of Beal juice in Nottingham for Halloween
Is it the old Beetlejuice or the new Beetlejuice?
I remember seeing the original Beetlejuice in the theaters and it's such a cool movie, you know, and I've watched it since several times
It's so funny. I don't know if the new one's any good. I don't know if the new one's any good, but
you know, I'm
Probably not gonna check it out. I love the originals. I hate remakes or you know, I don't like sequels that much, but I
Want to check that out. What other movies are as good that I well, there's a movie called I think
What's the one with that has a
It has Dakota Fanning and she goes into this woods and there's like a cult in the woods and they all have a double of themselves
I forgot what it's called, but
Anyone see that one I haven't I don't I haven't seen a movie in the theaters since
The great Gatsby I think 2012 or something like that so but 13 years since I've seen a movie in the theaters pretty crazy
So anyone want a reading in the chat? I'll do a I'll do some readings and if anyone wants a a longer reading I
Can put the information on the screen, but I'm happy to do free readings
You know for everybody that's the particular is good. Oops. I just made that screen smaller. Let me see you see reading
There's information if you like a longer reading
But I'm happy to do probably a five card free reading for anybody that wants
Even that woman last night that her name was Shannon or Sharon or something like that. There you go
Um
I think that I did a good reading for her even though you'd like a reading. Okay. Okay, Patrick. You got it
Anyone that says I'm just you know trying to
Grift or whatever. I'm happy to do free readings for anybody and I've always been this way. It's not it's just like oh, okay, so
Patrick you got first of all we have the King of Cups, okay?
And so this really means that you've come into
Like some emotional control of yourself and this one says welcome to the world of the emotionally balanced man
Okay, so I think that you know you may have gone through
Pretty emotional ups and downs, but you know now you're very self-contained and able to
You know manage manage these emotions and it's like you come into this king kingly energy. Okay, also
you know
You're able to help other people
With your emotional balance, okay, what else we got for Patrick that's
Okay, we also have this Knight of Swords. Okay, so this Knight of Swords is
Night of Swords is a fast-moving energy. Okay, that could be a you know an air sign right night of swords
This could be something somebody coming towards you with some kind of communication
So look out for this person they'd be rushing in rushing out with some fast-moving communication
Something to act on okay. We also have the emperor. Okay. This is all the kings in the deck. It is Emperor card
This is he has the ultimate it says ultimate authority rests with him
So you've got some a kind of a got some kind of kingly authority with all the of all the elements
also, you know, but what you say goes and
People respect you also. I see you coming into this. Okay, the three of cups. I see you kind of
Celebrating with some people three of cups also indicate a third-party situation
Okay, because whenever you add more than the two people a third person that always
kind of makes a triangle, right?
And so I think this is a, that is a vampire right there.
That's vampire I recognize there on the bar right.
But I see some celebrating going on, okay?
Two, three, four, okay, let's do a final card.
Okay, well, okay, well, we have this kind of,
this could lead to some kind of sadness or heartbreak,
but let me clarify that
because I don't like to leave on that note.
Okay.
If something might throw you off balance, but you're going to be able to maintain maintain this balance, okay?
Says a journey into equilibrium, so it's about you know staying balanced no matter what the waves are in your life you're gonna want to
Stay stay
Equalibrated focus balance and you'll get past any kind of sadness
Okay, that's what I got for you Patrick. I hope you like that reading
Buy a mat and do some yoga. Yes, that's a great idea. That is a great idea
Yoga is great
You know, it's an Indian
It was brought here by a param paramhamsa yoga Nanda
Some very wealthy people brought this Indian guru into United States and he basically taught yoga and look how popular it is now
I hope you like that
In anybody else one so hey Fred Alastair look Fred Alastair is absolutely. Oh, okay. Yeah
Well, you know, I've been doing Tarot actually longer than Emma and I actually you know
Not to discount her or anything, but she does call like the the cards major and minor Arcadia
Okay
It's arcana. Okay, but you know, it's okay. It's okay
So Fred, let me just make sure I hide you. You are sacrificed to the abyss. Okay. Bye. Bye and
Tell Emma I said hi by the way
Anyhow, let me get my hands washed of that fool
Yeah
You know, she's relatively new it I'm doing tarot. I don't know if you knew that but yeah
I've been doing Tara probably about 25 years longer than her, but anyhow, it's not a contest
Whatever
And I am a professional because
I wear yoga pants. I should get some lululemon for men. I don't know
Yeah
Your yoga master bends and that's pretty cool
Yeah, but I'm not gonna disparage any terror reader, you know, she she's great for what she does
I'm great for what I do. I've also
Let me see. I'm gonna show you my Etsy store too. You can go over to my Etsy store and read the review read the reviews
Let me see
psychewaken
Dot Etsy comm we see I do have my store up and running I have some I
Have some readings up there. There are 75% off
It's like your weekends, let's see.
Okay, yeah, there we are.
And you are welcome to check out my reviews.
I have 279 reviews, 1,800 sales, okay?
And go ahead and read those reviews.
Right now, I did delete my old listings
and so it kind of like takes away the rating,
but if you read the reviews, you'll see.
People were very are very into them. So let me see. Oh, did I take it off? Here you go. Bye, Spunky. I love ya
There you go
So that is my Etsy store and you're welcome to check that out and I
Have some really really cool
really cool
astrological readings on there
where I will create art and music
To you know to your with your reading and I will generate some stuff and it will be very personal and very unique
I don't see anybody else doing it. So, you know, so this was my idea
So I should copyright it, right?
so
Bye spunky. Love you, sweetheart. So there you go. You can check out that my at my Etsy store and I got some great readings up there
One two three I have eight
Let me see, yeah, I have eight different kinds of readings for astrology and for tarot readings.
And so check it out.
You can check it out and I think that you will be impressed.
Satisfaction guaranteed or your money back.
So hopefully everyone's doing really good.
Um, what are we gonna do today? Let me see. Let me put on I'll play my cat video. Do I have a cat video?
We like rocking out with the cats. Let me see
Where is it, let's see I
Don't even see it anymore. I
Did have one to do with cats
Is this one
now wake up in the morning who's there by my side my small in there it is
she burns and she cuddles she's always there for me my little kitty frenchy's the best you see
You
I love it.
I love that.
The best.
That is the best.
Oh, the Cult of Yarl.
I know who that is.
He's his next sacrifice.
Online Dark Tarot?
I'm gonna check it out.
By Cult of Yarl.
Human sacrifice to the abyss. Thank you for being a sacrifice for my show. Every sacrifice makes me ten times more popular
All I have to do is
Find the haters Satan loves them
Okay
What else how about how about the haters club song? I love the haters club
I write them.
Canada dry got gonged off, didn't even swim
Summer's spunky Marcy flashing, chaos on the feed
And here comes a porn bomb, oh lord we don't need
Welcome to the madness, welcome to the show
He's purring.
Christine's with Fuzzy Bear.
Arthur's stirring pots, like he's cooking up a scare.
Truckerado rumbles in.
Sammons chasing views.
DJ Electra's cartoon face is breaking all the rules.
Piranha's got the trolling game down too.
We've gone too far
We've turned the trolls into our own memoir
Welcome to the show, where every wild night becomes another end joke.
We're lapping through the chaos and making it great.
Psych awakens forever. Yeah, we love this fate.
All right, who's got this tongue in his hand?
Why is all this so tough?
Obviously, you're not reading the chat, so I need a mod that actually reads the chat.
Why is Arthur still talking?
Yeah.
But you didn't want to be a mod anyway, it's fine.
So, let's see.
Here it is.
Oh, you're flying at it.
I have to hide you.
My back that's real one not pretend welcome to the site
can pluck those feathers toss it in the pan make it fried all that noise you're
making can't hide the hurt
Welcome to the
new songs
You know if you missed it, I do have a this is a new song
In the glow of
like a secret sharp as a knife but maybe she's tired of the dangers life he
drops his shirt with a volunteer's pride she's smirking but softening some
Where the sto-
that was a good one. Yeah, that's some belly dancing. Oh, and thank you for all the sacrifices.
I just sacrificed the haters, right? Cha-cha-cha!
I like that Cthulhu one. I love HP Lovecraft, right? He did the Cthulhu stuff, yeah.
What a brilliant writer. He was kind of a
kind of an oddball that really in mind, right? And so he wrote the katulu and the
miskatonic and there's all these, you know, yagabai, yagabaioth, yaldaboth. Oh, hold on,
that's ostracism. Yeah, I think he's kind of based on, did I see the threes company one? No, post it.
Come and knock on our door
We've been waiting for you where the kisses are hers and hers and his threes company to well
Well, I get that person before they get mods
Jump on that, please. Let me see. Oh, oh
That's okay. It's okay. I got it. Oh
Oh
My light went out. Oh shit. I know why. Oh, no. I'm okay. Oh
Yeah, it's an L for you. I'm sorry. Sorry to the jackass that was typing. Oh, you got that
You see threes company
Oh, I like it
Who is your favorite 3's company person?
Mine's Chrissy.
Is that Jack?
Chrissy?
Janet?
Oh, shit
Okay, that's all I can play oh
Bits and prices, uh, mr. Furley. I love it
Or mr. Roper. Who is it? I
Like that it was season two Chrissy. Yeah, she didn't make it much past season two. Oh my gosh
We got the haters in here today guys a lot of sacrifices for me
Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye
Right to the, right to Cthulhu, they go.
Yeah.
Bye.
Bye-bye, bye-bye.
Mr. Roper was pretty horny, wasn't he?
I love Mr. Furley.
Don Knott's is a great face.
It's kind of like the screech of the 80s.
I love Mrs. Roper too, you know?
That was, she was great.
Guys when you see those people mods see those people it's just yeah to Cthulhu
So
Thinking of maybe like going to run to the coffee place or the bagel place and getting another coffee before they close
So it's almost 130. Yeah
Thank you. Thank you, Gotti. I
Know we got some really big idiots in here. Hey, what's up? Here's Natalie
Come on up, Natty.
I love Natty.
You wanna meet an awesome woman?
This is an awesome woman.
I hope she'll come.
Hey, what's up?
You see me?
Natalie.
Sorry, I mentioned that in plain old.
Okay, how are you doing?
I don't know if it's gonna work.
Hope you're doing good. Let me I'm gonna plug in my light again
No, no, it needs
Okay
I'm gonna plug in my light. I just need to my my little kitty cat and tearing up my cords
How's your day
There we go
Hey, Natty, you hear me
Queen Natalie
There's my internet my Wi-Fi is
It's okay acting up at the moon. Let me know when you can hear me. Oh, oh
Uh-oh, yeah, well this person that that person is on a on kick. I'm also semi-casting on kick right now
You know so I might get some people like advertising and stuff like that
Apologize for those a little bit long advertisement. Hey, just subscribe to me on kick. Hey, hertha prove it to me
Give me some uh, yeah, we've been sacrificing souls
You know only ones that are deserving of a sacrifice
There we go. I'm seeing all the posts now. Okay, here we go
Chat filter all messages. Okay
You love mr. Roper turned his head to camera and smiles. Hey Samantha, how are you?
Got but the haters are so obvious and then the hello hello
They're just kind of sad people. Hey Rudy you want to come up say hi
Mr.. Roogah. Oh
Look at this cat. Look at this beautiful cat. Hi. Hi you happy cat you a happy cat
It's okay kick is not I mean, it's like I believe in all platforms actually I keep seeing these oh, here's a YouTube
Here's a YouTube replacement or whatever and it's like
Some of these sites are like, oh, it looks like they were made in someone's basement and stuff. Hey, babe
I want to show you my this new website. I'm working on though guys. This is
Called it's called psyche verse dot
Okay, here we go. It's called psyche verse dot
Or is it let me see psyche verse dot or yeah
And let me show you what it looks like share
I'm pretty impressed with how well I've done on this.
Let me see.
Psycheverse, where are you?
Oh yeah, I had to go like that.
Check this out.
Okay.
So this is a Psycheverse.
Let me just get to the main page.
Go back, there we go.
Let me see.
Go home. Oh, yeah home. Okay, so this is a psyche verse. Okay, so there's psyche verse and
Here's what I've got on it so far. So I have my channel I have Alexander mayors and her IP to her channels up there
And then I've got
Hot mess summer and the talk your is channel. I got my traveling gypsy tarot. I got money for 20
I got prairie winds wildflower. I got DJ Electra fry. I got hack ride studios. I got the oceans. Woo
And so it will tell you when they're on when they're live
I need to fix it a little bit, you know, right, but that can you all streamers everyone's in this directory, right?
There's a little directory
Got some new section and you can apply if you want your channel feature here, too
There's like an a plot. Let's see. I think it looks pretty damn cool. It looks pretty good
I'm really proud of it and yeah
It's gonna be really cool. You can out there's also a sponsored banner section, you know, so
Hopefully I can yeah, there you go
Then you can apply to be a streamer on it
Contact, you know, it's out a little pretty cool
So that's what I'm working on right there
Let's see. I know just any kind of any kind of doxing you can just take off
You see
All messages, I don't even see that okay
This is already taking care of
Okay
I'm gonna just
Let me see. What was that? That's on kick, right? Oh, that's because that's the only place they can post now is on kick
And the I'm gonna disconnect the kick. Let me see it to disconnect that
Okay
There we go. Yeah, they figured out a way through the filter the chat filter. Yeah
Yep, I'm in Redondo Beach, right now like I've ever hidden that so
Let's see 115 I'm thinking about grabbing another copy
Yeah, I'll go grab another copy again because today's national copy day by the way I have 15 minutes before they close
And so I'm just gonna go run and refill my actually I'm not going to because
They're probably out of coffee right now.
You see my grabbing a burger?
They might have some though. It's worth a shot.
If I get there right now, they can brew some more.
Okay, I'm gonna go. I'm gonna go get some. Yeah, I'll be back.
I love you guys. Thank you.
They dox, they slander, they gaslight, they disrupt. But what if you had the ultimate
guide to shut them down? Introducing Trollopedia, your field manual to decode, expose and outsmart
internet trolls. From classic tactics like love bombing to modern swarm attacks, Trollopedia
breaks it all down. Know the playbook, flip the script, take back your power. Trollopedia.